NILOOFAR ARAZKHANI

Front-end Developer

Website: https://narzk.github.io/niloofararazkhani/ | Email: niloofararazkhani@gmail.com

PROFILE

Front-end developer who loves to build good front-end platforms. Over **4 years** of experience maximizing the potential of teams in both large companies and startups. I possess a demonstrated academic background in computer science. I am fast at learning new things and eager to find solutions to new problems.

SKILLS

+4 years experience: JavaScript | TypeScript | HTML | CSS | React | Redux | Mobx Others: Redux-thunk | Redux-saga | Redux toolkit | Next.js | NodeJs | styled-components | Sass | css-modules | Storybook | Git | Webpack | Jest | Cypress | React-testing-library | Axios | Restful-APIs | system design | CI/CD | Linux | Scrum | Agile

EXPERIENCE

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, SNAPP EXPRESS; TEHRAN, IRAN - MAY 2022- PRESENT

- Improved the performance of the website by 43%.
- Enhanced company sales by **30**% through the development of new features.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, <u>DIGIEXPRESS</u>; TEHRAN, IRAN – AUG 2021- MAY 2022

- Refined delivery time by **24**% by developing and enhancing a delivery application for a new way of delivering.
- Through the use of end-to-end testing by Cypress and unit testing by Jest, the company reduced the cost of the test significantly.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER, SNAPP FOOD; TEHRAN, IRAN - AUG 2018- AUG 2021

- Maintained and refactored the old codes which improved the user experience by 32%.
- Contributing to an integrated design system (using *storybook*) for projects in the company, accelerating productivity by around **38**%

EDUCATION

Sharif University; Tehran, Iran - PhD degree-Present

• Software Engineer - GPA: 4.25 (out of 5).

Amirkabir University; Tehran, Iran — Master's degree-2019

• Software Engineer Graduate- GPA: **4.25** (out of 5).

Amirkabir University; Tehran, Iran — Bachelor's degree-2016

• Computer Science Graduate- GPA: 3.87 (out of 5).

LANGUAGES

• English: Fluent | Persian: Native | French: Intermediate